<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<RelativeLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:background="#00254E"
    android:paddingBottom="@dimen/activity_vertical_margin"
    android:paddingLeft="@dimen/activity_horizontal_margin"
    android:paddingRight="@dimen/activity_horizontal_margin"
    android:paddingTop="@dimen/activity_vertical_margin"
    tools:context="com.example.rabel.after_test.AboutUs">
    <ScrollView
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content">
    <LinearLayout
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:orientation="vertical"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content">

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="The waves of globalization of knowledge, its expansion and dissemination have brought about a radical shift in the concept of Universities. A further shift is registered in dismantling the age-old notion that the State alone is to shoulder the burden of tertiary education and accommodating the Private Universities to share this national duty, of course, without making any compromise with academic excellence and other matrices of University education. Metropolitan University joined this historic shift to bring about quality University education at an affordable cost to the students at their doorsteps.\n\nMetropolitan University was established in 2003 by an eminent social worker, Dr. Toufique Rahman Chowdhury with the approval of the Ministry of Education under the Private University Act, 1992 (amended in 1998). This is a social commitment of Metropolitan University mainly to our nation for promoting better education to meet the changing needs of the globe in the 21st century. The University will serve the citizens of the home country and also of other countries through its instructions, research and outreach programmes and prepare them to meet the challenges of the global economy successfully.\n\n*Vision: A true education, a true nation and fostering the development mainly of our country.\n\n*Mission: Metropolitan University is working hard to make properly educated, technologically efficient, highly productive class citizens to attain glorious careers, enjoy enriched lives and make direct contribution to all people mainly of the country. We believe that our mission includes providing a world class student centred learning environment where the students would learn how to learn.MU equipped with professionally sound faculty members is dedicated to students’ overall success. An environment has been provided to the faculty members where they can develop their further teaching skills and contribute to the innovation and discovery of new knowledge by developing and using their research skills."
            android:textColor="#FFFFFF"
            android:textSize="16dp"
            />
        </LinearLayout>
    </ScrollView>
</RelativeLayout>
